

Profile

Oleh is an experienced developer and system analyst who now specializes in blockchain ecosystem development.

He is comfortable working with many languages and platforms and has recently dedicated himself to developing blockchain applications using Solidity, Rust and MongoDB. He also has wide range of and deep experience with blockchain game development, and a master's degree in applied software engineering.

He guaranteed a high quality of work and keep good communication. Working with a team of programmers during some of his projects, he provided readable, well commented and structured code.

His goal is to provide high-quality service and products to his clients. He always ensure follow-up support after project completion.

Employment History

Game Developer at MobiDev, Kharkiv

January 2017 — October 2018

- Developed an application for the government where you could apply for state funds.
- •Started the development of new microservice-based architecture with Docker and Node.js.
- •Created a company identity system as a microservice for other services using Node.js and OrientDB

Frontend Engineer at JSN, Zaporizhia

February 2019 — October 2019

Personal achievements:

- UE4 Full Modding Support (subclasses of 'Blueprint')
- Custom Saving / Loading Systems in UE4 and Unity
- Multiplayer / Lobby systems in UE4 (via BP Replication)
- Advanced AI Systems in UE4 and Unity
- Complete Desktop Level Editor in UE4
- Complete Mobile Level Editor in Unity

Blockchain - Solidity Developer at TrendLine Global, Kiev

February 2020 — October 2021

- Researched blockchain technology, smart contracts, and cryptocurrency exchange systems.
- Developed smart contracts on Ethereum and EOS.
- Configured and deployed a cryptocurrencies exchange named Peatio, along with all its many dependencies.
- Configured and deployed private Bitcoin, Ethereum, EO

Details

C. Kharkiv, Ukraine webcometsmart@gmail.com

Date of birth

1995/01/28

Nationality

Ukraine

Links

Github Profile Telegram Profile

Skills

Blockchain

Ethereum

DeFi

IDO

AMM

Smart Contract

NFT Marketplace

Cryptocurrency

Hardhat & Truffle

Unity

Node.is

React

Typescript

 ${\sf MongoDB}$

Git

Languages

Ukrainian

English

Tech. stack:

- Ethereum, Bitcoin, BSC, FMT, MATIC, NFT
- Smart Contract / Solidity, Rust
- Javascript / NodeJS / React / Next.js / React Native

Hobbies

Swimming, Basketball, Kickboxing, Sambo, Music

Education

Faculty of Engineering, Harkivs'ka Deržavna Akademija, Kharkov

September 2002 — August 2016

- Followed my passion in a core of engineering and architecture of software
- Excelled in web cloud service acknowledgment
- Pursued a Generalist Scholars grant to study software architecture
- Majoring in Computer Science and Information Technology.
- Mastering of Information Technology